Due to heavy rain, the next train is running
about twenty minutes behind.
We sincerely apologize for the
delay in service today.
I-I'm sorry!
It's okay.
The train sure is late, huh?
Yeah. I'm getting sleepy just waiting.
But I'm glad she's still here with me.
Today, we kissed for the first time.
This... isn't a dream, is it?
If I could tell my old self that
we'd really fall in love,
I wonder how I'd react.
Episode 12
My First Love
Whoa! Here. Here!
Let me guess.
Do you have a crush on that girl?
Huh?
You've been watching her this
whole time, haven't you?
Hit it higher!
I see now.
No wonder you keep coming out here
in the cold. That explains it.
N-No, you're wrong! I don't really...
have a crush on her.
She just picked up something
for me I dropped the other day.
Hmm...
Sorry!
It's okay, it's okay!
Goodness.
Excuse me!
Just be careful not to hit
it into the road, okay?
All right. Thank you very much.
A Boy's Chair
Thanks for waiting!
Now that's one nice girl.
Sorry!
Really? She just seems normal to me.
You sure don't get it, youngster.
It's normal to help people in need.
If you do something wrong,
it's normal to apologize.
Remember to say thank you.
But it's actually pretty difficult
to do "normal" things all the time.
I'm home.
Listen, Saki is just about to graduate.
He studied so hard for his entrance exam.
You should come home for a while.
Oh, Saki-kun. Welcome home.
Oh dear. Are you really going to say that?
Thank you, Auntie.
Is that my mom on the phone?
Um, well, yes. But they're having
a bit of an argument.
I'm not sure you'll get to talk to her today.
Ah! There, there!
For goodness sake!
He's your son, you stubborn fool!
Welcome home, Saki.
Thank you.
I can't find that monster anywhere!
Oh, I just saw him.
Really? Where is he?
Here, here.
Did you hear? Yao-kun asked
a girl in class 2 out!
Wow! He's got guts!
And then you know what?
Um... We still have cleaning to do.
I guess she doesn't like interrupting
when people are talking.
I can kind of relate.
But why do I keep thinking
about her so much?
The book I just borrowed
is really interesting!
A Boy's Chair
Oh? What kind of book is it?
What in the world am I doing?
Was she too shy to talk
to that lady at first?
It's actually pretty difficult
to do "normal" things all the time.
You're all going to be graduating soon.
So today, I'd like to give
you a special assignment.
Feb.14th
PE
Japanese
Math
English
Home Ec
Homeroom
Art
Some of you might end up at different
middle schools than your friends.
Name
Birthday
Star Sign/Blood Type
Dreams
Someone I Like
Something I Like
So before you graduate,
I want you to exchange these cards
with at least three people you
want to stay in touch with.
It's not like I have any friends. Can I
give them to people outside of school?
U-Um... Is this yours?
Oh!
Y-Yeah!
That card... We go to the same school, right?
That old man isn't here with you today.
She talked to me!
U-Um, well...
Are you going to give that card to someone?
I-I don't have any... m-many friends, so...
Neither do I.
I was worried I wouldn't have
anyone to give my last one to.
If it's okay with you, want
to exchange cards with me?
H-Huh?! Really?
But I haven't filled mine out yet.
That's okay! Just give it
to me at school later.
Can I just ask what your name is?
Mine's Hotaru. Hinase Hotaru.
M-My name is Sa... Saki.
Sasaki-kun, huh?
What?! That's not right!
If I correct her now, it might embarrass her!
Okay, I'll see you at school, Sasaki-kun!
Name: Hinase Hotaru
I don't have a cell phone.
Birthday
December 24th
Star Sign/Blood Type
Capricorn, Type O
Dreams
Eating yummy food from around the world
Something I like
Food
Fluffy things
Name: Hinase Hotaru
I don't have a cell phone.
Birthday
December 24th
Star Sign/Blood Type
Capricorn, Type O
I wish... I wish I could get
a girl like her to like me.
I wish she could be my soulmate.
What should I do? It's already March,
and I haven't given her my card yet.
I want to give it to her when we're alone.
Hey, isn't that Yao-kun?
Oh, you're right!
But who's that girl with him?
Huh? No way!
Graduation day is
At this rate, I'm not going to get this
to her before graduation.
Name: Hananoi Saki
Her shoes are still here!
Okay, I'll see you at school!
If she's in the classroom,
I'll give it to her.
I'll give it to her!
If she's in the classroom...
I told you all about how I felt, Hotaru-chan!
There's somebody else in there.
I told you he was my dream.
I told you I was really in love!
But you... But you...
You didn't consider my feelings
at all, Hotaru-chan.
Oh? You sure are late.
I thought you might not show up today.
I'm... a horrible person.
What's all this now? Did something
bad happen at school?
I should have stopped it.
I should have gotten a teacher.
I should have tried to cheer her up.
I should have done something. I couldn't.
Instead, I left her crying
all by herself. I...
I...
I couldn't do anything for her!
I never should have started liking her!
I don't know what happened,
but have yourself a good cry, sonny.
Despair is what teaches us how to grow up.
But you know, you shouldn't feel bad
for liking her. That isn't right.
Love is something you just fall into.
There's no such thing as someone
who shouldn't fall in love.
Thank you for your patience.
The train will arrive at
platform one momentarily.
Oh, s-sorry! When did I fall asleep?
Good morning. It's totally okay.
It was a nice little bonus, honestly.
I'm just trying to process my joy.
J-Joy?
Yeah. I'm happy.
I never thought I'd ever see her again.
I never thought she'd talk to me again.
Local Train
20 Minute Delay
Train will be arriving momentarily
All right, I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah.
See you tomorrow.
Hmm?
No, I was just thinking about
everything that happened today.
Um, anyway, I look forward
to keep seeing you tomorrow on, too!
Sure.
I never thought we'd fall in love.
But actually, I never bothered to ask
what happens after you're in love.
I was too focused on simply falling in love.
I never thought about what comes next.
My past is full of regrets. Will I ever
be able to talk to you about that?
If that day comes, this time, will I finally
have become someone worthy of you?
Hananoi-kun, I tried making sweets today!
Wow! I'm so happy!
Hotaru-chan, you have some
cream on your cheek.
I-I had another really weird dream!
The other day, Hananoi-kun and I
had our first kiss.
The aftermath is intense!
Hotaru-chan?
Are you feeling down today?
N-No, not at all!
Oh, the movie is gonna
start soon. We should go!
You're right.
This isn't the first time we've held hands,
but my heart always starts pounding!
But it's more than excitement.
I'm just so happy.
Is this what it means to like someone?
It's strange. I used to be
so scared.
Hmm? Is something wrong?
No.
I'm just so happy right now!
Why are all of the rings
here lined up in pairs?
Oh, because they're for couples.
They are?!
Would you like to try one on?
Huh?!
Wow!
If you put these rings together,
they form a heart.
Well, Hotaru-chan?
It's a very unfamiliar feeling!
Unfamiliar, huh?
Maybe a simpler design would be better.
U-Um, is this the sort of thing
people wear when they're in love?
They're popular with students as well.
B-But it might be a little too soon for us.
Are you sure? I still think it's a lovely
thing to celebrate your feelings.
Do you like them after all?
If it's all right, I'd like
to give you one as a present.
N-No, that's okay. They seem expensive...
They're super expensive!
Please stop by again sometime!
I guess that was too much.
Maybe a ring is overdoing it.
Oh.
Hotaru-chan?
S-Say, why don't we each buy
matching ones here?
Wow.
I've never worn a ring before.
Let's be careful not to lose them, okay?
I'm so happy.
I was worried this sort of thing
would embarrass you, Hotaru-chan.
I don't know. It's kind of nice to
commemorate our feelings like this.
I never knew what this felt like.
Huh?
That just holding hands could be so exciting.
The desire to make
someone dear to you smile.
Or how much courage it takes
to confess your feelings to someone.
I don't ever want to forget how that feels.
As long as I'm wearing this,
I'll remember whenever I look at it.
Oh! I'm a bit embarrassed I said that...
No, not at all.
Not even a little.
It sure is funny, though.
I was so scared of falling in love.
Hananoi-kun, you taught me what love is.
Thank you!
I'm the one who's grateful.
For falling in love with me...
Thank you.
Are you o—
Was I making a weird fa—
Not weird at all.
Sorry. You're just so cute, I couldn't resist.
I like you so much, Hotaru-chan.
Good morning, Hotaru-chan.
Good morning, Hananoi-kun!
My name is Hinase Hotaru.
I'm sixteen years old.
And Hananoi-kun and I...
We're in love!
Thanks so much for watching!
Ready?
Thank you very much!